

PROFILE

Hello! My name is K James. I'm a good full-stack developer having over 10 years of experience in developing web sites and our team specializes in developing windows applications and mobile applications. And also I'm interested in developing intelligence device that is controlled by mobile phone and it will be able to communicate with web application. In the future, I will try to develop the products that might be used to the lives of people. I think the credit is very important in cooperation and I will keep the credit. If you hire me, I will do my best and I will become a good developer for you.

CONTACT

PHONE: 389 77949320

WEBSITE:

EMAIL: k.james.dev@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Golf Billiards Football

K JAMES

Full-Stack developer

EDUCATION

Mt. High School
1998 - 2008
I graduated with a high school diploma.

Euro-Balkan University
2008 – 2011
I graduated and got Bachelor's degree

WORK EXPERIENCE

Reverse C Expert at Makedonski Telekom Jan. 2012 - Sep. 2016

At the first, I've studied about reverse engineering and got a good experience. I worked here as a c ++ expert for over 5 years.

Mobile & Web Developer at Makedonski Telekom June, 2013 - May, 2015

I worked as a mobile developer in Makedonski Telekom. Here I developed a lot of mobile applications such as chatting app, business app, restaurant app, hospital app, education etc.

Full-Stack Developer at J&W company

May, 2019 - Present

I'm a full-stack developer and project manager in **J&W**. So far, we have developed many web sites and services. Those are working correctly.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript
MySQL, PHP, MERN Stack
WordPress
Native Java, Kotlin, Swift
Python, C++, C#
Crypto, Reverse Engineering
OpenCV, Embedded System

